A Guide to the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Administration, Records, 1997-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
- Series XI. Legislative Files, 2002-2006., Extent: 145 folders. (Box 39-56)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1001-1100, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1101-1250, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1251-1400, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1401-1500, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Resolutions and Joint Resolutions, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 1-100, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 101-250, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 251-400, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 401-550, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 551-600, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 601-650, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 651-5002, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Action Summary Charts, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Proposals--Drafting Requests, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Proposals--Miscellaneous Documents, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Proposals--Senate Bills, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Proposals--Senate Bills, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Proposals--Senate Bills, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Studies, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Legislative Material, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Reviews of Carry-over Legislation--House Bills 73-469, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Reviews of Carry-over Legislation--House Bills 510-1010, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Reviews of Carry-over Legislation--House Bills 1016-1465, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Reviews of Carry-over Legislation--Senate Bills 102-650, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Contact Information, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 1492-1911, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 1920-2298, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 2326-2533, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 2539-2934, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 785-1003, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 1015-1323, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Legislation Introduction and Implementation Updates, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Legislation Introduction and Implementation Updates, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 542-1492, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1500-1600, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1601-1700, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1701-1800, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1801-1900, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1901-1930, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1931-2000, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2001-2100, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2101-2200, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2201-2350, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2351-2450, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2451-2550, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2551-2750, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2751-2900, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2901-2950, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 400-850, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 851-900, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 901-1000, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 1001-1100, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 1101-1200, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 1201-1350, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Proposals, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Proposals, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Proposals--Drafting Request Forms, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Proposals--House and Senate Bills, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Proposals--Miscellaneous Documents, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Proposals and Drafting Request Forms, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Series XII. Public Broadcasting Board, 1997-2006., Extent: 96 folders; 7 compact discs; 8 cassette tapes. (Box 56-65)
  Contains board meeting minutes, financial information, contracts, and reports which document the activities of the Virginia Public Broadcasting Board. The Public Broadcasting Board is the channel through which public television and radio stations (including the radio reading service), receive state financial support. It provides grants and contracts with stations that enable them to implement instructional television programs for schools and other community interest programs. Many files contain documents created by the Board during the administrations of Governors George Allen and James Gilmore, spanning the years 1997-2001. It is unclear how or why the files were included with the papers from the Warner administration. They may have been collected by Warner's Office of the Secretary of Administration, or they may have been abandoned when the previous administrations left office and merely added to the Warner files. Files of particular interest include those containing correspondence related to the funding campaign waged in an attempt to escape a devastating financial blow to public broadcasting during the 2002 budget crisis. Also of interest are the folders devoted to the digital conversion process undertaken in the late 1990s. The files containing detailed meeting transcripts, as well as those labeled "Board Meeting Packets" provide comprehensive information about the Board, its functions, and the issues public broadcasting faced. Additionally, the Master Plans for Public Telecommunications contain the blueprints for management of the statewide public broadcasting network of stations. The files are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Also included in this series are four sets of audio recordings of Public Broadcasting Board meetings. Tape recordings and recordings on compact disc are available for the following meetings: November 10, 1997, March 19, 1998, November 13, 2002, and for one unidentified meeting that possibly took place during 1997. Also included are three tapes of unrelated audio material, including recordings of radio show broadcasts and political campaign advertisements, all presumably from the 1990s. These tapes were not converted to compact disc because their contents are seemingly unrelated to the Board and its activities.
  - Agency Information--Audit Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Agency Information--Operational Structure, 1997-2001 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Audit Reports--Public Stations, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Biennium Budget Requests (2002-2004), 2001 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Biennium Budget Requests (2006-2008), 2005 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Board Meeting Packets, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Board Meeting Packets, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Board Meeting Packets, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Board Meeting Packets, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Board Meeting Packets, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Budget Committee Recommendations (2002-2004 Biennium), 2001 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Budget Material, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Budget Material, 1999-2001 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Community Service Grants, 1999-2000 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Contact Information, 1999-2000 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Contract Statements, 1997 June-July (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Contract Statements, 1997 August-September (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Contract Statements, 1997 October-December (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Contract Statements, 1998 January-February (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Contract Statements, 2001 May (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Contract Statements, 2001 June-July (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Contract Statements, 2001 August-September (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Contract Statements, 2001 October-November (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Contract Statements, 2001 December (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Contract Statements, 2003 June (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Contract Statements, 2004 October-December (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Contract Statements, 2004 December-2005 April (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Contracts--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 1999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Contracts--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 2000 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Contracts--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 2001 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Contracts--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 2002 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Contracts--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 2003 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Contracts--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 2004 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Contracts--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 2005 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Contracts--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 2006 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Contracts--Radio Reading Services, FY 2001 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Contracts--Radio Reading Services, FY 2002 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Contracts--Radio Reading Services, FY 2003 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Contracts--Radio Reading Services, FY 2004 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Contracts--Radio Reading Services, FY 2006 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence--Funding Campaign, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence--Funding Campaign, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence--Funding Campaign, 2004-2005 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Digital Conversion Information, 1999-2001 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Digital Conversion Information, 1999-2001 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Digital Conversion Information, 1999-2001 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Digital Television Grant Finances, 2000-2001 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Digital Television Grant Finances, 2000-2001 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - End-of-Year Reports, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1999-2001 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Grant and Financial Information, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Grant and Financial Information, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Grant and Financial Information, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Grant and Financial Information, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Grant Programs--Community Service Grants, FY 2001 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Grant Programs--Community Service Grants, FY 2002 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Grant Programs--Community Service Grants, FY 2002 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Grant Programs--Instructional Telecommunications Services, FY 2002 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Grant Programs--Radio Reading Services, FY 2002 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Legislation, 2003-2004 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Master Plan for Telecommunications, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Master Plan for Telecommunications--2006-20010 Blueprint for Public Telecommunications, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Agendas, 1999-2001 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Announcements, 2000-2001 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Information, 1997 July (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Information, 1997 August (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Information, 1997 November (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Information, 1998 February (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Information, 1997 March (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 1999 February (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 1999 June (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 1999 August (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 1999 September (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 2000 May (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 2000 September (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 2001 February (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 2001 May (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Transcripts (Budget Committee), 2001 July (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Transcripts, 2001 August (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Policies and Procedures for the Master Plan for Public Telecommunications, 1997-2003 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Public Telecommunications Facilities Program Grants, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Resolution of Gratitude--Kenneth D. Wright, II., n.d. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Strategic Plans for Public Television, 1998-2000 Biennium (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Statewide Instructional Telecommunications Survey, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - WVPT and WCVE Dispute, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Audio Recording (Compact Disc), Board Meeting, 1997 August 19 (Box 65, Item 8)
  - Audio Recording (Compact Disc), Board Meeting, 1997 November 10 (Box 65, Item 9)
  - Audio Recording (Compact Disc 1 of 2), Board Meeting, 1998 March 19 (Box 65, Item 10)
  - Audio Recording (Compact Disc 2 of 2), Board Meeting, 1997 August 19 (Box 65, Item 11)
  - Audio Recording (Compact Disc 1 of 2), Board Meeting, 2002 November 13 (Box 65, Item 12)
  - Audio Recording (Compact Disc 2 of 2), Board Meeting, 2002 November 13 (Box 65, Item 13)
  - Audio Recording (Compact Disc), Board Meeting, date unknown, possibly 1997 (Box 65, Item 14)
  - Audio Recording (Cassette Tape), Board Meeting, 1997 August 19 (Box 65, Item 15)
  - Audio Recording (Cassette Tape), Board Meeting, 1997 November 10 (Box 65, Item 16)
  - Audio Recording (Cassette Tape), Board Meeting, 1998 March 19 (Box 65, Item 17)
  - Audio Recording (Cassette Tape), Board Meeting, 2002 November 13 (Box 65, Item 18)
  - Audio Recording (Cassette Tape), Board Meeting, date unknown, possibly 1997 (Box 65, Item 19)
  - Audio Recording (Cassette Tape), Miscellaneous Radio Show Recordings, c. 1990s (Box 65, Item 20)
  - Audio Recording (Cassette Tape), Miscellaneous Radio Show Recordings, c. late 1990s (Box 65, Item 21)
  - Audio Recording (Cassette Tape), Delegate Barney Kidd Campaign Ads, c. 1990s (Box 65, Item 22)
- Series XIII. Real Property Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 31 folders. (Box 66-69)
  Contains correspondence, meeting minutes, reports and other material that document real property issues handled by the Department of General Services, which falls under the Secretary of Administration. Many of the files deal exclusively with issues involving the renovation of the Capitol Square complex in downtown Richmond. These records include reports, working papers and decision briefs that show the progression of the project throughout Governor Warner's administration. Well-documented issues include the proposed destruction and/or re-use of the 8th and 9th Street buildings, and the complete renovation of the Capitol building. There are also files that document the sale of what was known as "Old City Hall," in Richmond. Other files of note include meeting material and correspondence created by groups involved with various projects including the Capitol Square Preservation Council, the Virginia Capitol Preservation Foundation, and the Public Buildings Board. Material of particular interest found in the Public Buildings Board file includes a 2002 report which documents the then current conditions of the buildings in Capitol Square, while outlining potential projects.
  Also included in this series are several folders devoted to the Governor's Real Estate Initiative, Executive Order 75. This order was issued as a reengineering effort to transform the management of the Commonwealth's real estate portfolio. The initiative came from a recommendation of the Governor's Commission on Efficiency and Effectiveness and was one of Governor Warner's key priorities. The order prompted the state to engage in a review of its real estate management processes, including acquisitions, sales, easements and leases, with the goal of identifying ways to save money and improve management practices. The Secretary of Administration was to direct the program with the goals of increasing bargaining power, decreasing allocations, reducing total costs, all while maintaining agency security and operational needs, as well as functional space and real property services. All files are arranged alphabetically according to subject, and in some cases chronologically within the folders.
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project, 2002-2003 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project, 2004 February-July (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project, 2004 September-November (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project, 2004 December (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project--Capitol Square Preservation Council, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project--Public Buildings Board, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project--Virginia Capitol Preservation Foundation, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project--Virginia Capitol Preservation Foundation, 2004 January-March (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project--Virginia Capitol Preservation Foundation, 2004 April-June (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project--Virginia Capitol Preservation Foundation, 2004 July-December (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Square Complex Renovation Project--Virginia Capitol Preservation Foundation, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Real Estate Initiative, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Real Estate Initiative, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Real Estate Initiative, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Real Estate Initiative, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Old City Hall 2005 March-April (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Old City Hall 2005 May-August (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Old City Hall 2005 September (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Old City Hall 2005 October (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Real Property Management, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Real Property Management, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Real Property Management, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Real Property Management, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Real Property Management, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Real Property Management, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Real Property Management, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Real Property Management, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Real Property Management, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Real Property Management, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Real Property Management, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Series XIV. Special Projects Files: Electronic Procurement (eVA), 2002-2005., Extent: 9 folders. (Box 70)
  Contains correspondence, memorandums, decision briefs, reports and other working papers pertaining to eVA, the Commonwealth's electronic procurement system. eVA is an internet based electronic portal for procurement by state agencies and institutions. eVA serves as a single point of contact for vendors and suppliers to conduct business with state agencies and institutions. It makes the purchasing process much quicker, and allows access to more businesses and increased competition. The goal of eVA is to provide agencies with more choices and less costly goods. Having been implemented at the end of Governor Gilmore's term, eVA was a very new program when Governor Warner took office. The material found in this series documents problems the system faced, such as lagging involvement from agencies, and complaints that the system disproportionately excluded small business owners. The files also contain information on the successes the program achieved in its formative years, such as being nationally recognized as leading the way in electronic procurement. The files are arranged chronologically.
  - Electronic Procurement, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Procurement, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Procurement, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Procurement, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Procurement, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Procurement, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Procurement, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Electronic Procurement, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Procurement, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Series XV. Special Projects Files: Virginia Partners in Procurement, 2003-2004., Extent: 2 folders. (Box 71)
  Consists of two folders of correspondence, reports and other working documents related to the 2003 launch of the Virginia Partners in Procurement (VaPP) program. The purpose of this spend management initiative was to change the "buying culture" of the Commonwealth by collaboratively purchasing good and services, with the goal of saving money. Other key goals of the project were to facilitate the use of Virginia-wide contracts using the eVA system, and to improve the state's supplier diversity in terms of small, women owned and minority owned businesses. One item of interest is a copy of Governor Warner's July 24, 2003 speech given during the roll-out event for the VaPP program.
  - Virginia Partners in Procurement, 2003-2004 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Partners in Procurement, 2003-2004 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Series XVI. Veterans' Affairs Records, 2002-2005., Extent: 71 folders. (Box 71-79)
  Contains reports, correspondence, and other working papers which document veterans' issues in Virginia, and the activities of the Department of Veterans' Services (previously the Department of Veterans' Affairs). In 2002 Governor Warner issued Executive Order 15 which created the Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs. This commission was charged with providing recommendations on how to make the Commonwealth's veteran-oriented programs more effective by reviewing the agencies, programs and boards that serve the veteran community, assessing current and future needs, and identifying potential funding sources. The Commission was responsible for submitting a comprehensive report of its findings, which was published in December 2002. The final report is included in this series, as are a multitude of files which document meetings and other aspects of the Commission's research process. In response to the Commission's findings, Governor Warner issued Executive Order 40, which aimed to improve services for Virginia's veteran population. The Governor directed all state agencies to identify ways they could improve services for veterans in the areas of service delivery and preference in hiring. The order also directed the Secretary of Administration to give priority to efforts to obtain grants and other contributions for improving services to veterans.
  Many other veteran-specific programs are documented here, including the cemeteries in Amelia and Suffolk, Virginia. Information about the Virginia Veterans Care Centers in Richmond, and Roanoke, Virginia is also included. The Roanoke location folders are mostly devoted to issues surrounding the improper financial and personal actions of its executive director in 2002, and how the Board of Trustees and the Office of the Secretary of Administration worked together to correct the problems in order to keep the center operational. This series documents the involvement of Deputy Secretary Sheryl Bailey, and the Office's commitment to improving the services offered to Virginia Veterans.